{
    "subject": "resource/Collier_Memorial_State_Park",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Klamath_County,_Oregon",
    "human_readable": "Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789344668388367,
            "question": "Where in Oregon is Collier Memorial State Park located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.968254804611206,
            "question": "Is Collier Memorial State Park in Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9652417302131653,
            "question": "Is Klamath County home to Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9530362486839294,
            "question": "Name the state where Collier Memorial State Park is situated."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9294087290763855,
            "question": "Where is Collier Memorial State Park located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91265469789505,
            "question": "Which county contains Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783915042877197,
            "question": "What state is Collier Memorial State Park in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783726096153259,
            "question": "What is the location of Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677806258201599,
            "question": "Mention the county of Collier Memorial State Park."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8591012954711914,
            "question": "In what county can you find Collier Memorial State Park?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2714_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mention the county of Collier Memorial State Park.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2714_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of Collier Memorial State Park?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2714_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Collier Memorial State Park in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2714_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2714_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the provided context information, I can evaluate whether it supports the triple \"Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon.\"\n\nThe output is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the location of Collier Memorial State Park, specifically mentioning it is situated in Klamath County, Oregon. Therefore, the statement \"Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}